字幕转制｜天外生物
感谢原字幕制作者
卡罗尔 听我说 这风景不错 碧海蓝天 星光闪烁
I'll tell you, Carol, it's quite a sight up here. All those stars, the blue water.
这我想起在卡波岛的那晚 还记得吗
Reminds me of that night in Cabo.Remember?
哈尔 继续飞行
Hal, stay on the flight.
那晚喝了好多桑格利亚汽酒
A lot of sangria that night.
哇 你能回想起来吗 哈尔
Boy, could you put it away. Hal.
我都不知道那晚我们怎么回到旅馆的 哈尔 你正处于九万一千四百米的高度
I don't know how we made it to the hotel... Hal, you're at 91,400 feet.
再高十米窗户就碎了 你也会粉身碎骨
Ten feet higher, the window cracks and you're tapioca.
再推高一点点 也许我们可以为公司刷新记录
Just pushing it a little. Maybe we'll set a record for the company.
哈尔 别这样 这是你的第一次 正常发挥就好了
Please, Hal. For once in your life, no stunts, no surprises.
不准逞强
No surprises.
找到他
Find him.
乔丹先生 安全着陆我们的飞行就完美了
Make this landing and we'll have a perfect flight, Mr. Jordan.
这意味着我可以得金奖 或仅仅是一次超常模拟
So does this mean I get a gold star, or just an incredible simulation?
怎么没电了
What happened to the power?
有人么
Hello?
卡罗尔 有人吗
Carol? Anybody?
如果再让我驾驶这鬼东西的话
If I have to fly this freaking park ride again...
好吧
Okay.
天啊
My God.
别动
No.
没关系
It's all right.
我的死期已到
My time has come.
你会讲英语
You speak English.
不会
No.
是这个戒指
It's the ring.
它选择了你 戴上它
It has chosen you. Take it.
你现在就是绿灯侠了
You are now a Green Lantern...
宇宙保护者中的一员
...one of the protectors of the universe.
守护者会派人来找你
The Guardians will send for you.
灵活
Use...
使用
...the ring...
这个戒指
...wisely.
见鬼了
What the hell?
绿灯侠
首次飞行
当那道奇异的绿光消失时 模拟器就
...and when that weird glow cleared, the simulator was...
发生地震了吗
Was there an earthquake?
当然没关系了 但是要一个星期
I guess it's okay, but a whole week?
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我也不知道 可能去探探险 观光旅行
I don't know. I thought I'd do some exploring. See some new sights.
反正在设计模型上达成一致前也没什么事
Not much else to do until we get word on the prototype.
幸亏模拟器的损害还不是很严重
Well, at least the simulator wasn't damaged too badly.
卡罗尔 我要走了 有空了再打给你
Hey, Carol, gotta run. I'll call you from... wherever.
看来是真的
So it's true.
阿宾·苏已经死了
Abin Sur really is dead.
他的尸体呢
Where is his body?
问你呢 他的 随同飞船一块儿爆炸了
I said, where is...? It was blown up with the spacecraft.
我要把它拿下来
I want it off.
这个家伙都没有经过训练
The poozer's not even trained.
他已经在练习了
Someone's been practicing.
虽然还没有人指导
And without a manual.
大家都放手 可以吗
Let's all power down for a moment, shall we?
我想我们还没有相互介绍
I don't think we've been properly introduced.
我叫辛尼斯特罗
My name is Sinestro.
这是布迪卡 托玛·莱
This is Boodikka, Tomar Re...
还有我们帅气的基洛沃格
...and you've met our charming Kilowog.
你是 哈尔·乔丹
And you? Hal Jordan.
哈尔·乔丹
Well, Hal Jordan...
我们都是绿灯侠军团的
...we are members of the Green Lantern Corps...
从OA星球来的一股强大的星际间力量
...an elite, intergalactic force from the planet OA.
我们的上级是一群被称为守护者的不死之神
Our superiors are a group of immortals known as the Guardians.
他们应该派人来找我 是的
Yeah. They're supposed to send for me. That's right.
我们就是带你回去谈谈的
We're to bring you back for a little chat.
假如你在犹豫的话
And in case you're wondering...
这可不是请求
...this is not a request.
守护者没决定前这个戒指还不属于你
The ring isn't yours until the Guardians have decided.
好的 非常好
Okay. Very good.
托玛 麻烦你一下
Tomar, would you do the honors?
我们认为在类似地球飞船里 你会更舒服些
We thought the trip might be easier for you in a more earthly construct.
谢谢
Uh, thanks.
你必须要知道 地球人
You must understand, earthling...
绿灯侠军团是一个特许机构
...the Green Lantern Corps is a privileged organization.
并不是任何人都可以加入的
Not just anyone can join.
他们有着巨大的责任
There are tremendous commitments.
每一个成员负责
Each Lantern is responsible...
巡视宇宙三千六百个扇区中的一个
...for patrolling one of 3600 sectors of the universe.
但是 就像一个管辖区配一个警察吗
But... Sort of like one cop per precinct.
是的 我觉得是
Uh, yes. I... I suppose.
我叔叔曾是警察
My uncle was a cop.
是的 但是 在海滨城市警局工作了三十年
Yes, but... Thirty years on the Coast City police force.
他曾经让我负责开警笛 他人很好
He used to let me turn on the siren. Nice guy.
但这是远远不够的 绿灯侠的戒指是个复杂的工具
But more than that, the Green Lantern ring is a complex tool.
他需要使用者的精神高度集中
It takes someone with fierce concentration.
我想我已经会用了
I think I got the hang of it.
他确实是会用了
He's got the hang of it.
拉那卡
Ranakar.
我们何必对此浪费时间他是人类
Why are we even entertaining this? He's a human.
是啊 很难不考虑这一点
Yes, hard to get past that.
恐怕来自地球的人类在星际间没什么好名声
I'm afraid the human race of Earth does not have the most stellar reputation.
他们粗鲁 卑鄙 害怕并且不值得信任
The fact is humans are crude, base, fearful and untrustworthy.
还有臭味
Then there's the smell.
你不能瞧不起整个物种
You can't condemn an entire species.
甘瑟 这是你的一家之言
You've said it yourself, Ganthet.
但他们能延续这么长时间 也未尝不是一个奇迹
It's a wonder they've lasted this long.
也许你应该听我说说他们的暴行
Maybe you'd like me to list their atrocities.
或许人类真的能帮助我们
Maybe our human can help us.
也许他有他的优点
Maybe he has a few of his own.
听着 伙计 我并没有要求要这个戒指
Listen, buddy, I didn't ask for this ring.
如果你们想要回尽管拿去 我受够了你们的屁话
You want it back, take it, because I've had enough of this crap.
看来我们可以给他们加条罪行 就是无礼
Well, it appears we can add impertinence to their many qualities.
人类也有优点
The human has a point.
如果他像大家所说的那样不值得信任的话
If he were as unworthy as everyone says...
这个星系中没有能量能强迫戒指戴在他手上
...no power in the galaxy could have forced that ring on his finger.
但戒指就在那 与他合为一体
Yet there it is, at one with him.
各位守护者委员 我能说几句吗
Guardian Council, if I may speak.
辛尼斯特罗 请说
Please, Sinestro.
一四一七扇区的绿灯侠 已确认
The Lantern of Sector 1417 is recognized.
谢谢你 阿帕·阿里·阿帕萨
Thank you, Appa Ali Apsa.
我有个提议
I'd like to make a proposal.
请允许我来带这个人类 并考验他
Allow me to take the human under my wing, test him out...
看看他能不能胜任
...see what he's made of.
那是我的工作
That's my job.
只要稍加调教 每个人都会有所成就的
People can surprise you if you give them a little incentive.
辛尼斯特罗 你有更重要的事需要做
You have more important things on your agenda, Sinestro.
我们正面临危机
We have a deepening crisis at hand.
我知道 长官 但我认为这个人类也许可以帮助我们
I understand, sir, but I thought the human could be of assistance.
这有点反常规
It's a bit out of the ordinary...
但我对辛尼斯特罗的提议挺感兴趣
...but I'd be interested in Sinestro's evaluation.
要不我们来投票决定
Shall we put it to a vote?
大家开始吧
All in favor.
结果出来了 辛尼斯特罗 这个人就由你指挥
So be it. The human falls under your command, Sinestro.
祝好运
Good luck.
我是这的教练
I'm the trainer around here.
我知道 我知道
I know, I know.
现在什么状况 现在你是我的了
So, what now? Now, I own your ass.
我们走
Come on.
他们谈论的危机是指什么
What's the crisis they were talking about?
关乎谁将控制这个宇宙的小事
A small matter of who's gonna control the universe.
不过目前还处在最佳状态
Not that it's in the best hands as it is.
先做重要事情吧
But first things first.
地球人 你现在处的位置就是圣坛
You are on sacred ground, Earth boy.
我们处在宇宙的中心
We're at the center of the universe.
这个提灯包含着驱动所有戒指的能量
This lantern contains the battery that powers all the rings.
它同时储存有这个宇宙的所有已知信息
It also contains all the known information of the cosmos.
类似地图集 记载有宇宙的划分归属
A sort of atlas and who's who of space.
我们将去一二一五号扇区玩玩
We're going to be playing in Sector 1215.
你需要快速掌握这些信息
You need to be brought up to speed.
将你的指环对准光 用力想一二一五 剩下的事提灯电池会帮你完成
Stick your ring in the light, think 1215 and the battery will do the rest.
不可思议
Unbelievable.
这可不是旅行见闻讲演
This isn't a travelogue.
不错啊 上一个新兵把他的触角都烧没了
Not bad. The last rookie fried his antennas off.
多谢夸奖
Glad I could impress you.
但是你的确不错
But you do.
不像其他人 我喜欢人类
Unlike the others, I like humans.
我欣赏他们的精神 以及他们生来对权贵的蔑视
I admire their spirit and their natural contempt for authority.
这里却循规蹈矩
It's well-founded here.
你是指守护者
You mean the Guardians?
他们曾经极盛一时 不过现在也开始衰败了
They were a power at one time, but now they've grown soft.
他们对前线是什么样毫无概念
They've no idea what it's like on the front line.
不过别担心 地球人
But don't you worry, Earth boy.
他们会留心你的 我只想知道你有没有资质
They'll be taking notice of you. I need to know if you've got the stuff...
- 来处理这些事  - 什么事
- ...for what's ahead.  - What's that?
我们要找到杀阿宾·苏的凶手
We're going to get the butcher who killed Abin Sur.
凯德门岛是这个星球的藏污纳垢之处
Cadmendoh is a pustule of a planet.
这里到处都是犯罪人渣
A breeding ground of criminal scum.
我曾经建议我们用流星雨将这毁灭
One time I suggested we clean it out with a meteor shower.
守护者觉得我在开玩笑
The Guardians thought I was kidding.
我们在找谁 一个叫库驰的乌贼精
Who we after? A squidman named Cuch.
他杀了阿宾·苏吗
He killed Abin Sur?
笑着杀死他的
With a smile.
我提取的文件里没有这个地方
I don't have this place in my files.
这里是拉贝拉巢穴
It's called Labella's.
会经常变换地址
It changes addresses frequently.
他是拉贝拉吗
Is he Labella?
他只不过是个巨人
He's the bouncer.
闭上嘴 跟在我的后边
Watch my back and keep your mouth shut.
布雷瓦特
Boolywatt.
辛尼斯特罗
Sinestro.
看起来今晚很忙啊
Looks like a busy night.
库驰有没有出现过
Any chance Cuch has shown up?
我不知道 没有库驰这个人
Don't know no Cuch.
布雷 看看你
Booly, Booly, Booly. Look at you.
像个一无是处的橡胶球
Like a big rubber Booly ball.
信不信我可以将你弹着玩儿
Bet I could bounce you off the wall.
我发誓没见过他 我发誓
L... I haven't seen him. I swear!
你知道见到他时该找谁吧
You know who to come to when you do.
知道
Yeah.
也许我们应该来个“微服私访”
Maybe we should have come undercover.
有什么好玩的
What's the fun in that?
拉贝拉
Labella
辛大人
S-man.
宝贝 你来时应该通知我一声啊
You should've let me know you were coming, baby.
总带给我惊喜
Always surprising me.
为什么总是这样
Why you do that?
本来还可以好好玩一下
Could've made some cozy time.
亲爱的 我赶时间
I'm in a bit of a hurry, my dear.
我在找库驰
I'm looking for Cuch.
库驰
Cuch?
别来问我
Don't ask me.
我又不是他妈妈
I'm not his mother.
我听说他在这
I heard he was in town.
宝贝 库驰与昆虫人一块儿走的
Cuch left with the bug man, baby.
那已经是很久以前的事了
Long time ago.
从来没有回来过
Never come back to old Labella.
我怎么才能相信你
How come I don't believe you?
这些衣服怎么连拉链都没有
How come these suits got no zippers?
亲爱的 你大驾光临不会想跟我玩月光球吧
Aw, honey, you're not gonna slam Labella for a little moon ball.
我也不能控制所有到这的人啊
I can't control all the shank that gets in here.
拿着 什么
Take it. What?
一点刺激
A little incentive.
也许可以帮助你回忆
Maybe it will jog your memory.
开始吧
Go ahead.
辛大人 你真坏
You're a bad boy, S-man.
库驰呢
What about Cuch?
我告诉过你
I told you.
不
No.
再来一次
One more.
辛尼斯特罗 不要
Sinestro, come on.
他在哪 我不知道
Where is he? I don't know.
亲爱的 求求你了
Honey, I beg you...
库驰在哪
Where's Cuch?
我真的不知道
I don't know.
算了吧
End this.
我知道我在做什么
I know what I'm doing.
他做完一件事后总会回来找你的
He always comes back to you after a job.
求求你
Please...
他在这 就在附近 是不是
And he's here. He's close, isn't he?
告诉我吧 拉贝拉
Just tell me, Labella.
你什么意思 她在哪
What do you mean? Where is she?
拉贝拉
Labella!
攻击
Shoot.
我去追他
I'm going up.
是定时炸弹
Aah!
我运气好
I got lucky.
你敢违抗我
You defied me.
你差点杀死她
You could've killed her.
我告诉你 朋友
Let me tell you, friend.
控制局面的唯一方式就是制造恐惧
The only way to operate out here is by fear.
他们攻击 我就强势还击
They hit, I hit harder.
他们侵袭 我就摧毁他们
They attack, I annihilate.
对于暴乱 我坚决给与无懈可击的反击
I am the one constant, unassailable force against their chaos...
是你 让他们忽略了的这点
...and you made them forget that.
你以为我喜欢这样
You think I enjoy this?
看看守护者创造的这个宇宙
Look at the universe the Guardians have created.
我们是宇宙中力量最强的 但他们让我们干什么
We have the greatest power in the cosmos and what have they made us?
处理垃圾
Garbage collectors!
我们收拾各种垃圾
We pick up the trash.
小偷 杀手
A thief here, a killer there.
浮渣 尘土 污垢
Scum, dirt, filth!
永无止境 但这些可以被终止
There's no end to it, but there could be.
我的梦想是有一天 消除这一切腐朽
It's my dream that one day all this rot will be wiped away.
建立新秩序 一个可以结束混乱的秩序
A new order will prevail, one that will end the chaos...
但是心软没法解决问题
...but it Won't be built by the faint of heart.
你背着我手下留情了 地球人 这个我无法容忍
You got soft on me back there, Earth boy, and that I will not tolerate.
一切都好吗我们听到阵骚乱
Everything okay? We heard there was a disturbance.
没事
We're fine.
你逮到库驰了
Hey, you got Cuchie.
难得他这么安详
Don't he look peaceful.
我要把他带到最近的分站 你们和我一起来
I'm taking him to the nearest substation. I want everyone with me.
你没事吧 没事
You all right? Yeah.
很好
Swell.
介意我坐这吗
Mind if I join you?
这可能会影响你的声誉
Might hurt your reputation.
给他们点时间适应
Give them time.
你要知道的是
You have to understand...
阿宾·苏深受大家爱戴
...Abin Sur, everyone loved him.
他有家庭 朋友
He had family, friends.
他是不可取代的
He was irreplaceable.
库驰怎么样了
Any news on Cuch?
带去审讯了 谁审问
They took him to interrogation. Who's asking the questions?
你觉得呢
Who do you think?
天哪 我知道 辛尼斯特罗出手很狠
Ouch. I know. Sinestro can be difficult.
这么说吧 他有时很自以为是
All right, he can be pretty damn arrogant.
我们有些人开始担心他 但他压力很大
Some of us are starting to worry about him, but he's under a lot of pressure.
是的 拯救宇宙什么的 没错
Yeah, saving the universe or something. That's right.
库驰只是个小人物
Cuch is just a bit player.
我们真正在追踪的是他的头 坎加·罗
The one we're really after is his boss, Kanjar Ro.
他不过是个战争头子
He's just a warlord.
不再是了
Not anymore.
他找到了黄元素 我该记笔记吗
Not since he found the yellow element. Should I be taking notes?
这个故事可追溯到万物起源之初
This story goes back as far as time itself...
那时守护者是唯一具备感情的生物
...when the only sentient beings were the Guardians.
他们创造了提灯电池
They built the lantern battery...
这远远早于军团的创立
...long before the creation of the Corps.
这块电池可提供给所有戒指能量 依靠的就是绿元素
The battery would power all the rings with the green element...
即宇宙中最强大的能源
...the greatest energy source in the universe.
只有守护者知道它的出处
Where it comes from only the Guardians know.
它被安装那刻起 守护者就以此为杀手锏
But once it was installed, the Guardians had the ultimate weapon...
来维持银河系的和平和公正
...to maintain peace and promote justice in the galaxies.
不幸的是 这块电池 有一个漏洞：即黄元素
Unfortunately, the battery had one vulnerability, the color yellow.
它是光谱的一部分 能够抵制绿元素
It's one part of the light spectrum that can resist the green...
而黄色能量最集中的源头
...and the most concentrated source of yellow energy...
就是黄元素
...is the yellow element.
亿万年来 守护者把它封存在另一空间的地下
For eons, the Guardians had it hidden underground in another dimension...
直到被坎加·罗发现
...until Kanjar Ro found out.
当守护者意识到黄元素被盗
When the Guardians discovered the theft...
他们和高层绿灯侠召开了紧急会议
...they called for an emergency meeting with the senior Lanterns.
阿宾·苏自愿去做卧底
Abin Sur offered to go undercover.
几天后 他潜入了罗的飞船
Within days, he had infiltrated Ra's ship...
但未发现黄元素的踪影
...but there was no sign of the yellow element.
坎加·罗把它藏了起来
Kanjar Ro had taken it somewhere.
阿宾·苏正打算向守护者报告 结果被发现了
Abin Sur was about to report back to the Guardians when he was found out.
我听到的就是这样
That's the way I heard it.
阿宾·苏降落在了地球上
From there, Abin Sur made his way to Earth.
现在你代替了他 天啊
And now you're here. Jeez.
你一人抓获了库驰 他告诉你的吗
You captured Cuch by yourself. He tell you that?
不 我能潜入你大脑
No. I was in your head.
有意思
Interesting.
正如你们所知 阿宾·苏逃跑后
As you know, Kanjar Ro was forced to abandon his ship...
坎加·罗被迫遗弃了他的飞船
...after Abin Sur's escape.
现在他又开始行动了
Now he's on the move again.
我刚从库驰那得到消息
I just found out from Cuch...
罗和他的人最迟在一千七百个小时内会在卡典空间会合
...that Ro and his men are meeting at the Kadian Space Terminal at 1700 hours.
就这些总共就这些吗
That's it? That's all you got?
不是说它不重要
Not that it isn't significant.
不是这个意思 知道这个太好了 急需 很必要
No. It's good to know. Needed. Necessary even.
我命令所有人在一千六百个小时内回来
I want everyone back here at 1600 hours.
我们一起出发 有问题吗
We'll leave together. Are there any questions?
如果没有 那么
If not, then...
失陪
Excuse me.
我们已经不只一次谴责过你了 辛尼斯特罗
This is not the first time we've had to reprimand you, Sinestro.
我们守护者是不允许这种酷刑的
This cruelty is hardly the Guardian way.
他不配合
He was resistant.
阻碍了审讯
It made the process difficult.
我尽力而已 你应该通知我们
I did my best. We should have been called.
我们本可以使用通灵术套出真相
We might have been able to use our telepathy to draw him out.
没时间了
Time is running out.
我们正面对一个决意摧毁我们的敌人
And we're facing a foe who is hell-bent on destroying us.
绿灯军团是个典范 辛尼斯特罗
The Green Lantern Corps is an ideal, Sinestro.
你忽略了它的本意就无法维护它
You don't save it by ignoring what it stands for.
不允许同样的事发生在坎加·罗身上
This must not happen to Kanjar Ro.
一旦抓到他 立即送归我们处理
The moment he is captured, he is to be brought to us.
由我们来审讯
We'll do the questioning.
明白了吗
Is that understood?
明白
Yes, sir.
他们会毁了我们所有人
They will doom us all.
我需要有人守护外围 奇普
I'll need someone to watch this outer perimeter. Ch'p?
我总是干这种苦差事
I always get the stink jobs.
让新人来吧 我无所谓
Let the new guy do it. Whatever.
好吧 我们走
Fine. Let's go.
别被行李绊倒
Don't trip over the luggage.
游客们 请注意
Attention, travelers.
我们对服务的中断表示抱歉
We apologize for this interruption in service.
绿灯军团要求对太空站进行一次常规扫描
The Green Lantern Corps has requested a routine scan of the spaceport.
无需担心 活动片刻后恢复正常
There is nothing to be concerned about. Operations will resume momentarily.
那只红脸猪想把我揪出来
That red-faced swine wants to flush me out.
我们该怎么做
What should we do?
出去
Leave.
从这滚出去
The room. Get out.
我准备好了会通知你们
I'll let you know when I'm done.
我在这
I am here.
给我现身
Make yourself present.
辛尼斯特罗 我在呼叫你
Sinestro, I'm calling.
现身
Make your presence known.
我来了
I'm here.
你想玩什么把戏 想找你不容易
What kind of stunt are you trying to pull? You're a hard man to reach.
你想怎么样 每天向你报告
What do you want, a daily briefing?
即使像这样 我们谈话很危险 特别是阿宾·苏死后
It's dangerous to talk, even like this, especially with Abin Sur dead.
罗 交流只有两种方式
Communication, Ro. It goes two ways.
我发誓我不会把你挤出局
I swear I'm not squeezing you out.
黄元素在哪 在武器专家那儿
Where's the yellow element'? With the Weaponers.
武器都准备好了 我们没多少时间了
The weapon is ready for pickup. We don't have long.
在哪 你手下就在周围 你以为我会告诉你吗
Where? I'm gonna tell you surrounded by your pack dogs?
别考验我的忍耐力 罗
Don't try me, Ro.
我为此付出了一切 军团 未来 生命
I've put everything on the line for this: the Corps, the future, my life.
你休想搪塞过去
I am not going to be given the runaround.
这样吧 我们一起去武器专家那 就我们俩
Tell you what, we go to the Weaponers together, just you and me.
你摆脱你的人 我摆脱我的
You get rid of your boys, I'll get rid of mine.
去哪找你 等候室
Where are you? In a waiting room.
半小时后在五十号站点等你 但如果我发现任何一个绿灯侠
I'll meet you at Station 50 in half an hour. But if I see one ring anywhere...
去等着吧
Just be there.
托玛 计划改变
Tomar, we have a change of plans.
快点 我们这就出发
Come on. We're leaving.
但是绿灯军团
But the rings...
用隐身术
Use your faders.
乔丹
Jordan?
是不是抓到他了 还没 你这怎么样
Tell me you got him. Not yet. How are you doing?
到现在为止 我看到了十颗流星 一颗超新星还有一个行李员
So far I've seen 10 shooting stars, one supernova and a baggage handler.
托玛说辛尼斯特罗想把我们中大部分 重新部署到下一个站点
Tomar says Sinestro wants to re-deploy most of us to the next port.
到南区去 托玛在那等我们
Get over to the south perimeter. Tomar is meeting us there.
好吧
Uh-huh.
你没事吧
You Okay?
没事 我被什么东西砸中了
Yeah. Something hit me.
待在这
Stay here.
接招吧 昆虫人
Hold it, bug boy.
乔丹 你在哪
Jordan, where are you?
我在杀虫
Got a little pest-control problem.
坎加·罗在哪
Where is Kanjar Ro?
辛尼斯特罗 他正前往西门
Sinestro. He's heading for the west gates.
不论如何 抓活的
Do whatever it takes. I need him alive.
绿灯军团
Rings!
干的漂亮 哼
Nice move. Hm.
一个接一个
All right, one at a time.
你们在干嘛 罗在哪
What are you doing? Where's Ro?
辛尼斯特罗 这些人 这些人无关紧要
Sinestro, these people... These people are irrelevant.
组织在执行任务 给我记牢了
The Corps is on the line. Get that through your heads.
在抓到坎加·罗之前
None of us, and therefore none of them are safe...
所有人包括他们都没有安全保障
...until we get Kanjar Ro.
即使要把这变成废墟 我也不在乎
I don't care if we have to tear this place apart girder by girder.
是他
It's him.
推
Pushit
你没事吧 没事
You all right? Yeah.
干得好
Good shot.
他们要赶上来了 该减负了
They're going to reach us. Time to lighten the load.
该死
Holy crap!
我们得冲过去
We have to get through.
前头有个裂口 我们可以安全脱离
There's a rift ahead. We can get out home free.
是刚才在机场那家伙
It's that guy from the port.
你还坐在这干嘛
So why are you sitting here?
还剩一个
One bug left.
换做我 我会住手
I'd power down if I were you.
只有我知道武器专家在哪
I'm the only one who knows where the Weaponers are.
没有我 你永远找不到
Without me, you'll never find them.
跟我合伙 我就告诉你 我发誓
Take me in, and I'll implicate you, I swear.
拜托 辛尼斯特罗 放下戒指 我们还可以商量
Come on, Sinestro. Put the ring down. We can still work this out.
辛尼斯特罗 我在考虑
Sinestro? I'm thinking.
还想什么
What's there to think about?
B计划 也行得通
Plan B. It could work.
辛尼斯特罗
Sinestro.
是的
Yes.
在这
Down here.
你只身进入了驾驶舱
You entered the pilot's cabin on your own.
是的
Yes, sir.
你没看见坎加·罗 没有
And you did not see Kanjar Ro? No, sir.
你不记得自己杀了他
And you have no recollection of killing him?
我没杀他
I did not kill him.
有人杀了他 是你们中的一个
Someone did, and he wore a Green Lantern ring.
你是第一个到那的
You were the first ones there.
事实上 托玛·莱和布迪卡先到的
Actually, Tomar Re and Boodikka arrived on the scene first...
不过我片刻后也赶到了
...but I was there soon after.
我们分开跟踪飞船的水汽尾迹
We followed the ship's vapor trail separately.
飞船上再没别人了 没有了
And no one else was on the ship? No.
但我可以理解他的行为
But I think it's perfectly understandable what happened.
这个人类受到坎加·罗的攻击
The human was attacked by Kanjar Ro...
在他还剩一丝意识时 进行了反击
...and in his last moments of consciousness, he struck back.
明显属于自卫
A clear case of self-defense.
他不该这么做
He should never have put himself in that situation.
如果不是因为他逞英雄
If he hadn't played hero...
你们或许就能赶上飞船 并活捉坎加·罗
...you might have caught up with the ship and taken Kanjar Ro alive.
现在没人知道黄元素的下落
Now there's no telling into whose hands the yellow element might fall.
或许你有话要说
Perhaps you'd like to say something?
我没杀他
I didn't kill him.
那谁杀的
Then who did?
拿走他能量棒的人 我保证手上没有
Whoever took his Energi-Rod. I sure as hell don't have it.
你轻率的行动
By your brash actions...
已经把宇宙搞得动荡混乱
...you have placed the universe in absolute turmoil.
打断一下 是在你们管辖下
Excuse me, but the turmoil began...
黄元素被盗的那刻起 宇宙就开始动荡
...when the yellow element was stolen under your watch.
不要再说了 的确如此
We've heard enough. Indeed.
哈尔·乔丹 此次审判中你缺乏纪律性
Hal Jordan, it greatly disappoints me that in the judgment of this tribunal...
已经无法在继续履行绿灯侠的职责
...you have been found of insufficient discipline...
我们对此非常失望
...to carry on the duties of a Green Lantern.
警卫官上前一步
Will the sergeant-at-arms please come forth?
把戒指上交给基洛沃格长官
You shall hand your ring over to Commander Kilowog.
基洛沃格 守护者找到继承者前戒指由你保管
Kilowog, you will keep the ring until the Guardians choose its successor.
黄元素怎么办
And what of the yellow element?
我建议守护者开个特别会议
I suggest we call a special session with our honor guard...
讨论下后续战略
...to devise our next strategy.
我会安排的 长官
I can arrange that, sir.
没什么了的话 本次审判结束
If there is nothing more, this tribunal is over.
你们来送我回家吗
Are you my ride home?
我们是志愿来的 基洛沃格有话对你说
We both volunteered. Kilowog has something to say to you.
抱歉之前我对你的评价
I'm sorry I said the things I said about you.
你救了我 你是个勇敢无畏的绿灯侠
You saved my life. You are a brave and bold Green Lantern.
谢谢 基洛沃格
Thanks, Kilowog.
还吃吗 你吃吧
You gonna eat that? Go for it.
难熬的一天 抱歉
Quite a day, huh? I'm sorry.
他是那么平静 你注意到没 谁
Did you notice how calm he was? Who?
辛尼斯特罗 他竟然愚蠢的替我辩护
Sinestro. He even defended me, in a half-assed way.
他一直挺官僚的
He's always been political.
他知道守护者们隐藏黄元素的事情吗
Would he have known where the Guardians hid the yellow element?
他们相信他 他憎恨他们
They trust him. He hates them, you know.
他总爱挑刺
He's critical.
不 不 他受不了他们
Uh-uh. No, no. He can't stand them.
守护者说能量棒可能有用什么意思
What did the Guardian mean when he said the Energi-Rod might be helpful?
坎加·罗通过思想控制能量棒 里面也许存留一些心灵感应信息
Kanjar Ro controlled it through his thoughts. It might contain some psionic information.
比如黄元素放在哪里吗
Like where he put the yellow element?
拉那卡啥也不懂
Ranakar doesn't know his butt from his poozer.
即便他有能量棒
Even if you had the rod...
没有坎加·罗的脑电波也没法用
...you can't use it without Kanjar Ra's brainwaves...
信息就会被永远存封
...and that transmitter has been shut off for good.
准备好了吗 我们急着出发吗
Are you ready? Are we in a hurry?
这个就是
This is him.
我知道挺冷的 坎加·罗
I know it's cold, Kanjar Ro.
抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
我在哪
Where. . .?
你在棺材里 你死了
You're in the morgue. You're dead.
死了 我杀了你
Dead? I killed you.
我要接通感应体获取些信息 不会太久的
I'm reconnecting synapses for some information. This shouldn't take long.
还记得黄元素吗
You remember the yellow element, right?
黄色
Yellow.
你让武器专家看护着 他们在哪里
You left it with the Weaponers. Where are they?
科沃
Qwar...
再给你次机会
One more time.
科沃
Qwar...
或许我能指给我看 坐起来吧
Perhaps you can show me. Let's sit up, shall we?
开始吧 武器专家在哪里 黄元素在哪里
All right, now. Where are the Weaponers? Where is the yellow element?
三二四区 非常好
Sector 324. Very good.
能更准确点吗
Can you be more specific?
科沃德
Qward.
最近的披萨店也找到了吗
Can you find the nearest pizza joint too?
真是惊喜啊
Well, well, this is a surprise.
怎么回事 辛尼斯特罗
What's going on, Sinestro?
很明显啊 基洛沃格
It's fairly evident, Kilowog.
我在努力找到黄元素
I've been working behind the scenes to find the yellow element.
是你杀了坎加·罗
You killed Kanjar Ro.
帮他逃脱了惩罚
To save his hide.
小心点 你们不想伤到能量棒
Careful now. You don't want to damage the Energi-Rod.
我听说这物质很不稳定啊
The core is quite unstable, I've been told.
你对守护者撒谎了
You lied to the Guardians.
我对所有人都撒谎了 我是迫不得已
I've lied to everyone. I've had to.
为什么 好好想想
Why? Think about it.
坎加·罗怎么会知道黄元素在哪里
How did Kanjar Ro know exactly where to find the yellow element?
阿宾·苏怎么会这么快就死了
How was Abin Sur killed so quickly?
你的意思是有内鬼 没错
Are you saying there's a traitor? Of course.
为什么我想跟地球人合作呢
Why do you think I wanted to work with Earth boy?
起码我知道他是清白的
At least I could be sure he was clean.
你该对守护者说实话
You should've told the Guardians.
到时候再说吧
In due time.
先找到黄元素 基洛沃格
Let's get the yellow element first, Kilowog.
到时我们就是英雄了
Then we'll all be heroes.
摘掉你的戒指
Take off your ring.
别开玩笑了 布迪卡
Don't be ridiculous. Boodikka?
抱歉 辛尼斯特罗 你说不通这个家伙
Sorry, Sinestro. I don't think you can talk your way out of this one.
他还活着
He's still alive.
如果她杀了他 戒指会自动回到守护者那里
If she had killed him, his ring would have flown to the Guardians.
那样可就不太好了
And we'd rather not have that happen just yet.
来这里是乔丹的主意 我以为你已经走了
It was Jordan's idea to come here. I was hoping you'd be gone by now.
我告诉你了他很聪明
I told you he was bright.
你耍我
You played me.
我得进入你的思想 确定是否拉你入伙
I needed to get inside your head, see if you should join our club.
但是你很难懂啊
But you're not easy to read.
私下里我们再聊聊
We really need to talk about personal space.
现在还不晚 乔丹
It's not too late, Jordan.
布迪卡相信我 别人也会的
Boodikka believes in my vision. Others will too.
我得利用有点骨气的你把事情搞定
But I could use someone like you who has the stones to get things done.
那些矮人放弃了你
While the gnomes banish you...
我给你能力 无法想像的能力
...I offer you power, more power than you can imagine.
只要你能效忠于我
All I ask is for is your loyalty.
我在你手上了 还是回到刚才那段
Now, you see, you had me. Right up until that last part.
我以为人类会不太一样
And I thought humans were different.
收拾他
Take care of him.
把尸体和罗的放在一起 我得走了
You can hide his body with Ra's. I shouldn't be long.
偷袭我 是吧
Knock me out, will you?
人类
Humans.
天哪
Good God.
你就是武器专家吧
You're a Weaponer.
我是来找黄元素的
I'm here for the yellow element.
该来的不应该是你
You are not the one.
坎加·罗死了 我是他的同伙
Kanjar Ro is dead. I was his partner.
他告诉我来科沃德拿武器
He told me to come to Qward to pick the weapon up here.
他为之付出代价 现在是我的
He paid for it and now it's mine.
听好 我现在没有时间
Listen, I don't have time for this. I...
你的朋友
Your friend...
来晚了
...is late.
武器被没收了
The weapon is now in forfeiture.
该你来拿走了
It is yours to take.
这是控制戒指
This is your control.
我们的工作完成了
Our work is done.
该回自己的世界了
We leave this world to return to our own.
这个武器急具杀伤力
The weapon is a mighty force.
是你们的宇宙里最强大 最绝对的
The most powerful and absolute in your universe.
唯有一个例外
With one exception.
一个
One...
小小的
...slight...
缺陷
...imperfection.
是什么？
What?
每个武器都有的缺陷
The imperfection every weapon has.
就是使用者
Its user.
他们抓到布迪卡
So they got Boodikka.
独自开始 独自结束
I start alone, I end alone.
守护者想要见你
The Guardians want to see you.
我也正想见他们
And I them.
你在做什么啊辛尼斯特罗
What are you doing, Sinestro?
万不得已的事情 托玛
Only what's necessary, Tomar.
别那么郁闷 整个宇宙归矮子管有点太大了
Oh, don't look so glum. The universe has become too big for the gnomes.
新的世纪开启了
There's a new day dawning.
新的太阳升起了
A new sun rising.
他曾是我们最优秀的绿灯侠 是大家的榜样
He was our most brilliant Lantern. A paragon of duty and service.
他们中最聪明的一个
The cleverest of them all.
也许太聪明了 拉那卡 我们之前该预料到的
Perhaps too clever, Ranakar. We should have seen the signs.
辛尼斯特罗向大家解释之前 我还是很怀疑
Until Sinestro gets an opportunity to explain himself, I remain skeptical.
有件事可以肯定 你冤枉了好人
One thing's for sure, you took the ring off the wrong guy.
如果是我 应该归还给他
You ask me, you should give it back.
你觉得合适的时候
When you're ready.
没有能量了
It's lost its power.
托玛
Tomar.
他把他们都杀了
He killed them all.
看来是真的
So it is true.
甘瑟 新的政权即将到来
Yes, Ganthet. A new command is at hand.
新的政权 你好大的胆子
A new authority. How dare you?
- 这是篡权  - 闭嘴 你这个愚蠢的矮子
- It's an affront to...  - Shut your mouth, you stupid little troll!
你们无非就是一群吵死人的矮子 既没用又碍事
You're nothing but a clutch of bickering old biddies, ineffectual and obstructionist.
在星球里高呼秩序却看不到外面的世界
In a galaxy screaming for order, you have cast a deaf ear...
这些现在结束了
...but all that ends now.
你们说的那些守护神
As demigods bound by your word...
你们都要拜倒到我的脚下
...all of you are going to pledge your undying allegiance to me.
去死吧
Like hell!
拉那卡 这次我们同意
For once, Ranakar, we agree.
去死吧 辛尼斯特罗
Give this up, Sinestro.
我知道放弃权利是件难事
It must be difficult to relinquish power.
给你们点刺激吧
Let me give you some incentive.
你们将一无所有 最后命都保不住
You will have nothing. Not even your lives, in the end.
走了
Gotta go, guy
退后
Stand back.
谢谢
Good man.
怎么回事
What the hell?
开心的坠落吧
Happy landings.
没用了
It's dead.
绿灯侠们
The Lanterns.
没有能量和保护的绿灯侠们
Yes, all the ones in space, with no power and no protection.
没有军队的战争是不可能获胜的
You are generals without an army, in a war you cannot win.
还要死多少人
How many more have to die?
够了 辛尼斯特罗 求你了
Enough, Sinestro. Please.
我们遵从你的命令
We will accede to your demands.
拜托 变绿啊
Come on, get green!
他妈的
Oh, son of a...
戒指给我
The rings. Now.
说实话 基洛沃格 你不会有好下场的
Frankly, Kilowog, you weren't going to survive this anyway.
我会被诅咒的
I'll be damned.
你以为我曾是绿灯侠
And you thought I was green before.
乔丹
Jordan.
你看到他了
Do you see him?
看不出来
I can't tell.
这混蛋一定在什么地方
The bastard's here somewhere.
该结束了 辛尼斯特罗
It's over, Sinestro.
戒指上还有许多能量呢 足够打败你的
I still have plenty of juice left in this ring. Enough to take yours for insurance.
你还不够强大
You're not strong enough.
来点刺激点的吧
Just takes a little incentive.
对不起 笨蛋
Excuse me, poozer.
乔丹 能听到我吗
Jordan, can you hear me?
快回答 乔丹
Come in, Jordan.
你在哪里啊
Where are you?
正在下坠 我忘带降落伞了
Falling. I forgot my chute.
很有创意嘛
Very creative.
我也能来点小把戏
Hey, I got a few tricks too.
虽然我们要继续悼念
Though we continue to mourn those who have fallen...
在最近发生的背叛事件中逝去的人们
...during the tragic betrayal of recent days...
但是我们还要庆祝恢复原状
...we also celebrate our resiliency.
绿灯电池已经修复 戒指再度闪耀
Our battery is repaired, our rings replenished...
与黑暗势力斗争亦将继续
...and our battle against the dark forces continues.
我们从上一次斗争中学到了
If we have learned anything from our last battle...
黑暗势力会滋长于难以预料的角落
...it is that great evil can arise from the most unexpected sources...
值得庆幸的是 英雄主义也会胜出
...but, most thankfully, so can great heroism.
我邀请甘瑟带领我们发誓
I've asked Ganthet to lead us in our pledge.
如果不介意的话 阿帕·阿里·阿帕萨
If you don't mind, Appa Ali Apsa...
我想将此殊荣授予新绿灯侠 哈尔·乔丹
...I'd like to give that privilege to our newest Lantern, Hal Jordan.
好啊 好啊
Hear, hear.
怎么回事啊
What's the matter?
我早上才听说的
I just learned the thing this morning.
在最明亮的日子
n brightest day...
在最黑暗的夜里 只要我们在黑暗势力无处可躲
In blackest night, no evil shall escape my sight.
让那些追随邪恶力量的人们
Let those who worship evil's might...
感触到我们的力量 绿灯侠
...beware my power, Green Lantern's light!
我要走了
I'm off.
你打算去哪里
Where are you going?
我要去那边的老板处打卡了
I've gotta go punch a clock with my other boss.
这将会是一个很漫长的旅程
I can see where this is gonna be a long commute.